Tianna Mosby

804-467-7533 | mosbyts@vcu.edu | LinkedIn | Portfolio | GitHub

SUMMARY

An energetic, enthusiastic and creative developer with experience in software engineering including programming, databasing, server management and more. Tremendously self-motivated and highly skilled with the desire to lead and support the development, implementation and maintenance of responsive websites and applications. Certified Full Stack Developer through the University of Richmond. Brings a digital marketing perspective to web applications with demonstrated success in digital media platform management, content creation and advertising.

EDUCATION

University of Richmond | Richmond, VA Full Stack Web Developer Certification

P1 Learning, P1 Futures Program | Richmond, VA Interactive Advertising Bureau (IAB) Digital Media Sales Certification

Virginia Commonwealth University | Richmond, VA

Bachelor of Science in Mass Communications
Honors and Activities: Cum Laude, Dean's List, Vice President of Disney Appreciation Club

SKILLS

- JavaScript and jQuery
- Node and Express
- ❖ WordPress CMS
- MySQL and MongoDB
- HTML, CSS and Bootstrap
- Adobe Systems and Microsoft Office
- React
- Cisco Meraki and Umbrella
- Salesforce and Bullhorn CRMs

EXPERIENCE

Henrico Too Smart 2 Start | Henrico, VA Public Relations Specialist | **02/2020-Present**

Train and lead the public relations team to increase community awareness on substance abuse prevention through consistent voice and reliable presence online. Develop, edit and implement digital media marketing campaigns. Update website content to encourage community participation through prevention education and participation. Design physical and digital creatives to be posted in local community spaces and on social media platforms. Assist with grant writing and copy-editing documents.

Social Media Coordinator | 02/2019-02/2020

Astyra Corporation | Richmond, VA

Corporate Communications Specialist | 04/2019-Present

Develops and executes the company's branding campaigns through social media platforms, quarterly newsletters and employee outreach communications. Measures and reports on the effectiveness of said communications activities and use analytics to improve digital marketing strategy. Curates visual and written content that increases audience interaction and presence on company website, blog and social media pages through research and Search Engine Optimization (SEO) practices.

Provides in-person technical support for application, hardware, telephone and network-related issues. Manages the IT department's documentation, asset management and the development and implementation of policies, standards and processes. Acts as the manager for IT interns and entry-level employees and creates custom training plans.

Operations Admin and Executive Assistant | 04/2018-03/2019

PROJECTS

Charity Match

React Developer

Charity Match connects donors and volunteers to potential non-profits to assist based on the user's preferences and allows user to find a local chapter to volunteer with, visit the website and view the mission statement.

Created with:

- MongoDB/Mongoose
- Express
- React/Semantic UI React
- Node
- Charity Navigator and Google Maps APIs
- Animate On Scroll (AOS)

Tacky Holiday

Web Developer

The Tacky Holiday Website is a fun holiday site that allows the user to search any gif, laugh at holiday-themed jokes, read about the top elves of the year and enjoy the snowfall.

Created with:

- Giphy API/AJAX call
- JavaScript/jQuery
- Snowfall.js
- HTML/CSS/Bootstrap

Bamazon Store

App Developer and Database Engineer

The Bamazon Store is the low-budget version of an Amazon-like storefront that is run in the user's terminal. In this app, the user can virtually purchase common items with real-time databasing used to update the products' quantities.

Created with:

- MySQL
- JavaScript/jQuery
- Inquirer (JSON package)
- Terminal (Git Bash)

Hitchhikers' Travel App

Developer and Debugger

This GitHub deployed web application helps users plan their future trip using a single website. Instead of browsing the web for local attractions, weather information, traffic alerts and crime rates, the user can find all this information at the one-stop-shop Hitchhikers' Travel App.

Created with:

- JavaScript/jQuery
- Various API's/AJAX calls
- HTML/CSS/Bootstrap
- AOS (Animate On Scroll)
- Animate.css